Elle Sundberg

Baltimore, MD 21230 218-821-7492 elle@juranek.com

Summary

I have worked for 2.5 years as a social media manager in the hospitality and CPG sectors. I am passionate about social media because of it's unique ability to connect you with your most loyal customers and cultivate a fan base for your brand. I am self-motivated while eager to learn from others and continuously grow.

Skills

- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Canva
- Microsoft Office

- Hootsuite
- Copywriting in brand tone of voice
- Writing and reporting via Substack

Experience

Social Media Community Specialist, 02/2024 — Current

McCormick & Co Inc — Hunt Valley, MD

- Create organic social media content for condiment brands (Frank's Red Hot, Cholula, French's & Stubb's), across all social channels, from ideation to execution.
- Engage with online communities to foster a deeper love for the product and connection to the brand. Respond to comments and dm's using brand's tone of voice consistently across all platforms.
- Monitor social platforms for trends and relevant cultural moments to participate in.
- Analyze organic social media metrics and report on a monthly and quarterly basis. Create PowerPoint presentations as needed with engagement metrics from viral or tentpole moments.
- Collaborate with the larger global marketing team to align organic social efforts with the company-wide marketing priorities.

Social Media Manager, 05/2022 — Current

Contractor

- Create engaging content for local restaurant's social media feeds.
- Interact with communities online to foster a deeper love and connection to the restaurant.
- Address concerns and requests from customers online, discern solutions, and occasionally escalate to management.
- Design branding, guidelines, and in-store marketing materials for clients.

Marketing Intern, 04/2021 — 08/2021

GrowthZone — Nisswa, MN

- Monitored relevant conversations on social media and created a weekly report with findings for executive team.
- Wrote industry-relevant blog articles that drove SEO results.
- Created social media content and presentations.

Education and Training

04/2022 Grand Canyon University — Phoenix, AZ

Bachelor of Science Marketing

• 3.85 GPA

Portfolio & Blog

https://www.behance.net/ellejuranek

https://ellesundberg.substack.com

- Over the last 6 months I have cultivated a community of 2k+ subscribers.
- 5 of my posts have reached top 5 on the platform in the Fashion & Beauty category.
- Reading and writing about what is happening in different categories has helped make me a more well-rounded social media specialist.